Finding Aid for the Irene Haupt Photographs of June in Buffalo, 2018
State University of New York at Buffalo. Music Library
- Composer David Felder speaks with JoAnn Falletta, conductor during rehearsal of Felder's piece Jeu de Tarot at June in Buffalo 2018, 2018-06-10, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_0133.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0081_230.tif)
- Composer David Felder speaks with JoAnn Falletta, conductor during rehearsal of Felder's piece Jeu de Tarot at June in Buffalo 2018, 2018-06-10, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_0136.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0081_231.tif)
- Composer David Felder speaks with JoAnn Falletta, conductor during rehearsal of Felder's piece Jeu de Tarot at June in Buffalo 2018, 2018-06-10, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_0137.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0081_232.tif)
- Composer David Felder speaks with JoAnn Falletta, conductor during rehearsal of Felder's piece Jeu de Tarot at June in Buffalo 2018, 2018-06-10, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_0139.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0081_233.tif)
- Composer David Felder speaks with JoAnn Falletta, conductor during rehearsal of Felder's piece Jeu de Tarot at June in Buffalo 2018, 2018-06-10, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_0140.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0081_234.tif)
- Composer David Felder speaks with JoAnn Falletta, conductor during rehearsal of Felder's piece Jeu de Tarot at June in Buffalo 2018, 2018-06-10, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_0141.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0081_235.tif)
- Composer David Felder speaks with JoAnn Falletta, conductor during rehearsal of Felder's piece Jeu de Tarot at June in Buffalo 2018, 2018-06-10, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_0142.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0081_236.tif)
- Composer David Felder speaks with JoAnn Falletta, conductor during rehearsal of Felder's piece Jeu de Tarot at June in Buffalo 2018, 2018-06-10, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_0145.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0081_237.tif)
- JoAnn Falletta, conductor leads the Buffalo Philharmonic Orchestra in rehearsal at June in Buffalo 2018, 2018-06-10, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_0149.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0081_238.tif)
- JoAnn Falletta, conductor leads the Buffalo Philharmonic Orchestra in rehearsal at June in Buffalo 2018, 2018-06-10, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_0153.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0081_239.tif)
- JoAnn Falletta, conductor leads the Buffalo Philharmonic Orchestra in rehearsal at June in Buffalo 2018, 2018-06-10, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_0156.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0081_240.tif)
- JoAnn Falletta, conductor leads the Buffalo Philharmonic Orchestra in rehearsal at June in Buffalo 2018, 2018-06-10, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_0163.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0081_241.tif)
- JoAnn Falletta, conductor leads the Buffalo Philharmonic Orchestra in rehearsal at June in Buffalo 2018, 2018-06-10, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_0165.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0081_242.tif)
- Composer David Felder speaks with JoAnn Falletta, conductor during rehearsal of Felder's piece Jeu de Tarot at June in Buffalo 2018, 2018-06-10, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_0166.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0081_243.tif)
- Composer John Harbison speaks with JoAnn Falletta, conductor during rehearsal of Harbison's pieces Darkbloom: Overture for an Imagined Opera and Remembering Gatsby (Foxtrot for Orchestra) at June in Buffalo 2018, 2018-06-10, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_0169.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0081_244.tif)
- Composer John Harbison speaks with JoAnn Falletta, conductor during rehearsal of Harbison's pieces Darkbloom: Overture for an Imagined Opera and Remembering Gatsby (Foxtrot for Orchestra) at June in Buffalo 2018, 2018-06-10, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_0174.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0081_245.tif)
- Composer John Harbison speaks with JoAnn Falletta, conductor during rehearsal of Harbison's pieces Darkbloom: Overture for an Imagined Opera and Remembering Gatsby (Foxtrot for Orchestra) at June in Buffalo 2018, 2018-06-10, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_0175.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0081_246.tif)
- Composer John Harbison speaks with JoAnn Falletta, conductor during rehearsal of Harbison's pieces Darkbloom: Overture for an Imagined Opera and Remembering Gatsby (Foxtrot for Orchestra) at June in Buffalo 2018, 2018-06-10, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_0176.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0081_247.tif)
- Composer John Harbison speaks with JoAnn Falletta, conductor during rehearsal of Harbison's pieces Darkbloom: Overture for an Imagined Opera and Remembering Gatsby (Foxtrot for Orchestra) at June in Buffalo 2018, 2018-06-10, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_0177.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0081_248.tif)
- Composer John Harbison speaks with JoAnn Falletta, conductor during rehearsal of Harbison's pieces Darkbloom: Overture for an Imagined Opera and Remembering Gatsby (Foxtrot for Orchestra) at June in Buffalo 2018, 2018-06-10, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_0178.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0081_249.tif)
- Composer John Harbison speaks with JoAnn Falletta, conductor during rehearsal of Harbison's pieces Darkbloom: Overture for an Imagined Opera and Remembering Gatsby (Foxtrot for Orchestra) at June in Buffalo 2018, 2018-06-10, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_0179.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0081_250.tif)
Search Terms
The following terms have been used to index the description of this collection in the Library's online catalog.
Subjects
June in Buffalo (Festival) (Buffalo, N.Y.)--Photographs; Composers--Photographs; Music festivals--New York (State)--Buffalo--Photographs; Musicians--Photographs
Genres
Digital photographs; Portrait photographs
Associated Material
Related Resources
Related Resources in the Music Library
Irene Haupt Photographs of June in Buffalo 2000
Mus. Arc. 18
Finding aid for collection of photographs for 2000 June in Buffalo.
Irene Haupt Photographs of June in Buffalo 2001
Mus. Arc. 19
Finding aid for collection of photographs for 2001 June in Buffalo.
Irene Haupt Photographs of June in Buffalo 2002
Mus. Arc. 20
Finding aid for collection of photographs for 2002 June in Buffalo.
Irene Haupt Photographs of June in Buffalo 2003
Mus. Arc. 21
Finding aid for collection of photographs for 2003 June in Buffalo.
Irene Haupt Photographs of June in Buffalo 2004
Mus. Arc. 25
Finding aid for collection of photographs for 2004 June in Buffalo.
Irene Haupt Photographs of June in Buffalo 2005
Mus. Arc. 27
Finding aid for collection of photographs for 2005 June in Buffalo.
Irene Haupt Photographs of June in Buffalo 2006
Mus. Arc. 29
Finding aid for collection of photographs for 2006 June in Buffalo.
Irene Haupt Photographs of June in Buffalo 2007
Mus. Arc. 38
Finding aid for collection of photographs for 2007 June in Buffalo.
Irene Haupt Photographs of June in Buffalo 2008
Mus. Arc. 39
Finding aid for collection of photographs for 2008 June in Buffalo.
Irene Haupt Photographs of June in Buffalo 2009
Mus. Arc. 50
Finding aid for collection of photographs for 2009 June in Buffalo.
Irene Haupt Photographs of June in Buffalo 2010
Mus. Arc. 55
Finding aid for collection of photographs for 2010 June in Buffalo.
Irene Haupt Photographs of June in Buffalo 2011
Mus. Arc. 56
Finding aid for collection of photographs for 2011 June in Buffalo.
Irene Haupt Photographs of June in Buffalo 2012
Mus. Arc. 60
Finding aid for collection of photographs for 2012 June in Buffalo.
Irene Haupt Photographs of June in Buffalo 2013
Mus. Arc. 66
Finding aid for collection of photographs for 2013 June in Buffalo.
Irene Haupt Photographs of June in Buffalo 2014
Mus. Arc. 67
Finding aid for collection of photographs for 2014 June in Buffalo.
Irene Haupt Photographs of June in Buffalo 2015
Mus. Arc. 74
Finding aid for collection of photographs for 2015 June in Buffalo.
Irene Haupt Photographs of June in Buffalo 2016
Mus. Arc. 79
Finding aid for collection of photographs for 2016 June in Buffalo.
June in Buffalo Photograph Collection
A selection of images from the June in Buffalo festivals are available through University at Buffalo Libraries Digital Collections.